thebleeder.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy

* * *

Privacy Policy Updated July 24, 2008

We recognize that privacy (especially _your privacy_ ) is important. By creating and adhering to this Policy, we hope to protect your personal information, and ensure your visits to our site are safe and enjoyable.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through postal mail, telephone, and/or email to admin(at)zunehomes.com.  

## Information we collect, and how we use it

We do not collect your email address nor any other personal information about you. We won't send you any email offers or junk mail. 

We are just affiliate website of Clickbank's system and send users to final product website. We recongize that your personal details will not be shared with anyone.

When you make your purchase, you get taken to a shopping cart hosted by [Clickbank](http://www.clickbank.com/), a third party company which processes almost all of our payments. Clickbank collects your payment information in order to put through your order. You may read Clickbank's [privacy policy here](http://www.clickbank.com/legal/privacy.html). (Link opens in a new window.) 

We does not store your credit card information. However, Clickbank, according to its privacy policy "may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, email address, credit card number." 

When you buy, you will be taken to a page on the Product site which provides you with the special download material.

Like most websites, we usually send cookies to your browser when you visit our site. A cookie is simply a small file that identifies your browser. We use the cookies to track overall trends so that we can improve the user experience of customers who browse to our site. Cookies are entirely optional, and if you disable cookies on your Internet browser, you should still be able to browse our sites with no problem. 

When you write to our support email address, we may store the email you sent us so that we'll have it in our records. Certain emails praising us may be used as testimonials for our marketing, provided you do not object.
